Guide to the N. Scott Momaday Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Papers, 1788-2012; 1950s-2012
  - Paone, Anthony S.J. My Daily Life Confraternity of the Precious Blood, 1970, (Natachee's book), circa 1970s (Box 28)
  - Guest book with names, undated (Box 28)
  - The Story of Easter and an exercise book written in by Natachee, undated (Box 28)
  - "Navajo Stories: Book 1" written by Natachee, undated (Box 28)
  - Manuscript of The Moon in Two Windows revised September 29, 2000., circa 2000s (Box 28)
  - Two microfilms from the National Archive dated 1934, numbered 983-1 and 983-2, circa 1930s (Box 28)
  - Northland Press 1975 Book List Owl in the Cedar Tree by Natachee list on page 4, circa 1970s (Box 28)
  - Letter for Natachee from Barbara Mauldinm, the curator at the Museum of New Mexico regarding her basket collection, with photographs of the baskets. 1983, circa 1980s (Box 28)
  - Blank stationary with Envelopes (Owl on the paper), undated (Box 28)
  - Natachee Correspondence with family members 1950s-1970s (She notes that is may help with family genealogy), circa 1950s (Box 28)
  - Navajo Stories by Natachee, books 1, 2, & 3, undated (Box 28)
  - The Sponsor pamphlet, 1960; "My Grandmother" by Natachee; "Kee and Jack" by Natachee; "At School" by Natachee; Article "School Art Echoes Tribal Past by Natachee, circa 1960s (Box 28)
  - Manuscripts of Owl in the Cedar Tree including the original manuscript and correspondence with publishers, undated (Box 28)
  - Numerous news small news clippings regarding the Momaday Family, c. 1960s-1970s, circa 1960s (Box 28)
  - Short stories by Natachee: "Magic Moccasins", Caviar and Cornbread"; Beginnings of Natachee's autobiography, undated (Box 28)
  - "Grandmother's House" by Natachee with comments attached from a friend Doris?, undated (Box 28)
  - Natachee's notebook with handwritten short stories, undated (Box 28)
  - Short stories by Natachee no titles, undated (Box 28)
  - "Cupid was a Cadet" by Natachee, undated (Box 28)
  - Research on Acoma and Pueblo utility baskets, undated (Box 28)
  - Outlines and writings by Natachee, undated (Box 28)
  - Writings by Natachee "The Beginning", undated (Box 28)
  - Drafts and pieces of Natachee's autobiography, undated (Box 28)
  - Natachee's handwritten short stories, including "Miss Fanny", "The Cornfield"; Typed: "Thunderboy", "Drums and a Prayer", "Little Red", Papers under the pen name "Ann Ellis Scott"- "Feud Finished" "Cycle of Life", undated (Box 28)
  - Article by Natachee "Art is Where You Find It" with a note from F. Louis Hoover, editor for the Arts and Activities: Creative Activities for the Classroom, 1956. (Box 28)
  - Natachee writing about NSM around the time Ancient Child was published, undated (Box 28)
  - Stack of religious postcards; Pamphlet for Artigianato Artistico; Photographs from Italy?; Pictures from France?; Postcards from Italy and France; Pamphlet from Spello Italy and a card from Spello, undated (Box 29)
  - Newspaper clippings c. 1970s some regarding the Momaday family, some regarding local news, circa 1970s (Box 29)
  - Newspaper clippings, c. 1970s some regarding Natachee book readings, On is a poem by NSM in a newspaper; Article about Natachee earning an honorary degree at UNM with NSM as the speaker; Many articles on Natachee, circa 1970s (Box 29)
  - Minutes and paperwork from the Arts Standards Committee of the Native American Cultural and Educational Authority, June 8, 1999. and information regarding the Oklahomans of the century, 2000, circa 2000s (Box 29)
  - Seating list for the Fiftieth Anniversary Dinner, Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1962; Untitled writings by Natachee; Copy of the magazine New Mexico, 1949, With Natachee's article "Drum and Prayer Plumes" under the pen-name Ann Ellis Scott; an article in The Desert Magazine "Night with the Navajo" under the pen-name Ann Ellis Scott, 1950; Copy of "Navajo Stories: Book 3", circa 1950s (Box 29)
  - Framed print of a little girl, undated (Box 29)
  - Newspapers c. 1970 with articles regarding different tribes and local news, circa 1970s (Box 29)
  - Newspapers c. 1968 with articles regarding different tribes and local news, circa 1960s (Box 29)
  - Newspapers c. 1966-68 with articles regarding different tribes and local news, circa 1960s (Box 29)
  - Newspapers c. 1966-68 with articles regarding different tribes and local news, circa 1960s (Box 29)
  - Newspapers c. 1970s with a mix of articles, some pertaining to the Momaday family, but many regarding local events, circa 1970s (Box 29)
  - Newspapers c. 1980s coving the American Indian Expo and the Santa Fe Market, circa 1980s (Box 29)
  - Newspapers c. 1990 covering various Native and local issues, circa 1990s (Box 29)
  - Jemez Thunder papers from Oct. 1, 1996 covering Natachee's death., circa 1990s (Box 29)
  - undated newspaper clippings covering Navajo Long Walk (Box 29)
  - Arizona Highways Jan 1974; Southwestern Indian Ceremonials by Tom Bahti, 1971, circa 1970s (Box 29)
  - Letter from the University of Oklahoma Press regarding the return of manuscripts, 5 CDs and 2 Floppys and 1 Photo. These are all from the book Three Plays; Envelope with the discs and Arizona magazine is included., undated (Box 29)
  - Manuscript of Three Plays, undated (Box 29)
  - Manuscript of Three Plays, undated (Box 29)
  - Photograph of the Kiowa School, undated (Box 29)
  - Manuscript The Moon in Two Windows, undated (Box 29)
  - Law Book: Crane on Partnership. Hornbook Series, 2nd ed. West Publishing, 1952, circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: Walter Gellhorn, Administrative Law: Cases and Comments, 2nd ed. The Foundation Press, Inc., 1947, circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: Warren A. Seavey and Livingston Hall. Law of Agency: American Casebook Series. West Publishing, 1956, circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: Virginia Law Review, April 1951, circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: Willard W. Beatty, Education for Action: Selected Articles from Indian Education, 1936-43. United State Indian Service, 1944., circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: Miles O. Price and Harry Bitner, Effective Legal Research, Prentice-Hill, Inc. 1953, circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: Law of Contracts, revised Ed. Baker, Voorhis & Co., 1938, circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: James Casner and Barton Leach, Cases and Text on Property. Little Brown and Company, 1951, circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: Henry Campbell, Black's Law Dictionary. West Publishing, 1951., circa 1950s (Box 31)
  - Law Book: Ray Andrews Brown. The Law of Personal Property. Callaghan & Company, 1955, circa 1950s (Box 32)
  - Law Book: Justin Miller. Handbook of Criminal Law. West Publishing, 1934, circa 1950s (Box 32)
  - Law Book: E. Blythe Stason. The Law of Administrative Tribunal. 2nd ed. Callaghan & Company, 1947, circa 1950s (Box 32)
  - Law Book: Edwin W. Patterson and George W. Goble. Cases on Contracts. 3rd ed. The Foundation Press, Inc. 1949, circa 1950s (Box 32)
  - Law Book: Jerome Hall. Case and Readings on Criminal Law and Procedure. Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc. 1949, circa 1950s (Box 32)
  - Law Book: J. Forrester Davison and Nathan D. Grundstein. Cases and Readings on Administrative Law. Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc. 1952, circa 1950s (Box 32)
  - Law Book: William L. Prosser, Handbook of The Law of Torts, 2nd ed. West Publishing Co. 1955, circa 1950s (Box 32)
  - Binder of reproductions of photos and material in the National Archives pertaining to boarding schools and other research, undated (Box 33)
  - Binder of reproductions of photos and material in the National Archives pertaining to boarding schools and other research, undated (Box 33)
  - International Achievement Summit, 2003 binder with the program, and list of honor delegates, circa 2000s (Box 33)
  - International Achievement Summit, 2006 binder with the program, and list of honor delegates, circa 2000s (Box 33)
  - International Achievement Summit, 2007 binder with the program, and list of honor delegates. The binder also contains name badges for NSM and Barbara Glenn Momaday, circa 2000s (Box 33)
  - Pipe, 11" long, undated (Box 34)
  - Pipe, 6" long, undated (Box 34)
  - Souvaner horn from Lincoln's Birthplace, Kentucky. 6 1/2" long, undated (Box 34)
  - Stetch of the Taime, the must sacred bundle of the Kiowa by Carolyn K. Walker in frame, 8x10", undated (Box 34)
  - Portrait of NSM (4x6) in an 8x10 frame, undated (Box 34)
  - Silver bowl from the state of New Mexico presented as the Governor's Award for Excellence in the Arts, NSM for literature, presented by Governor Gary E. Johnson, 1996., circa 1990s (Box 35)
  - Ceramic plate from Governor Brad Henry's Inauguration, 2007., circa 2000s (Box 36)
  - Al Momaday judges badge from ENIPC Artists and Craftsman Show Pojoaque Pueblo, 1975., circa 1970s (Box 34)
  - Bolo tie, undated (Box 34)
  - NSM Honorary doctorate from University of Massachussettes, 1975 rolled with the ribbons around it. Note: This should be flattened if possible but was kept in this manner durring the premilinary inventory to maintain the relationship between the document and the ribbons., circa 1970s (Box 34)
  - Springfield Republican newspaper dated Feb. 28, 1866 with a story on Authors. Letters to Margaret T. Clark and Mrs. Orton Loring Clark, dating to the 1940s; Letters to Mrs. Frederick Tuckerman all from an envelope of material to NSM from Northhampton, MA, 1954, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Letter from Wm. H. Jackson to Mr. and Mrs. Orton Clark; Newspaper clippings of NSM; travel receipts to Paris, undated (Box 37)
  - Correspondence regarding a portrait of Edward Tuckerman by Alan Burroughs, 1947; Letters to the Clark family regarding the Portrait by Stuart, 1945; Letter from Frederick Tuckerman, 1881; Portraits on Edward Tuckerman, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Letters to the Clark family, c. 1940s regarding the Boston Museum of Fine Arts, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Photos of NSM receiving his first honorary degree from Central Michigan University addresses to Al and Natachee Momaday; Contact prints of negatives of the Momaday family, undated (Box 37)
  - Photos of NSM and family; Photo of NSM daughters; contact prints of negatives of the family., undated (Box 37)
  - Letters to and from Emily and Charles Tennyson (Copies) c. 1870s., circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Program and newspaper coverage of NSM Bicentenntial Lecture "A Nation of Nations: A House Made of Dawn", 1975, circa 1970s (Box 37)
  - Copies of letters and notes to and from Emily Dickenson and "Emily Dickinson: Creating the Poems" by Thomas H. Johnson, 1953, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Photocopy of Tuckerman letters, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Photocopies of research materials on Tuckerman, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Photocopies of research materials on Nathaniel Hawthorne, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Photocopies of research materials on William Cullen Bryant, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Photocopies of research materials on John Stone, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Photocopies of research materials on Tuckerman, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Photocopies of research materials on Ralph Waldo Emerson, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Part 1 of Binder labeled "Political Analysis of the State of New Mexico, dates inside on the handwritten note are from 1956 with tabs labeled for each class, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Part 2 of Binder labeled "Political Analysis of the State of New Mexico, dates inside on the handwritten note are from 1956 with tabs labeled for each class, circa 1950s (Box 37)
  - Picture of art or page from a book "M.p.th.f. 94, 2v (Graduale, in die beati Andree) Verkleinerung auf 82%"; Article on Americans for Inidian Opportunity with NSM picture, circa 1970s (Box 38)
  - Newspaper articles on NSM c. 1960s; Article "Conscious Questioning" by NSM from newspaper; envelope of newsclippings; Article on NSM winning the Pulitzer prize, circa 1960s (Box 38)
  - Folder of materials from a presentation in France, 2003, circa 2000s (Box 38)
  - Family photographs c. 1934-1970 of NSM and Natachee mostly; NSM Master's degree diploma for Stanford; NSM advertisement for car washes, circa 1950s (Box 38)
  - Beautifully designed letters from Frederica Matta in France, c. 2001., circa 2000s (Box 38)
  - Portraits of unknown persons in a mat folder, undated (Box 38)
  - Rolled-up and tied letter from Jill to NSM, undated (Box 38)
  - Glass framed artwork from NSM, undated (Box 39)
  - Glass framed artwork from NSM, undated (Box 39)
  - Statement of Service for Hercules Scott who served as Captain in Company G, 24th Regiment, Kemper's Brigade and Frank McMillan, served as 2nd Sergeant in Campany E 7th Regiment Cavalry. Both served as confederate soldiers in the Civil War.Documents in a glass frame and dated 1956., circa 1950s (Box 39)
  - Glass Award, undated (Box 39)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides mailed to Al Momaday, Jemez Pueblo, 1964., circa 1960s (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "Stonehenge Jemez", undated (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides Labeled: "Orosi & Sequoia", undated (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides of a parade to Al Momaday, 1955, circa 1950s (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "Helen Scy? NY 1977", circa 1970s (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "Jemez Country", 1957, circa 1950s (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "Wyo-Yellowstone" 1956, circa 1950s (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "USSR and US Track", undated (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "Ceremonials" 1958, circa 1950s (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "Wyo Country" 1957, circa 1950s (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "Indian City - Jemez Country", undated (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "N.Y.", undated (Box 41)
  - Box of 2¾x2¾ photographic slides unlabeled. Family photos: Natachee with grandchildren, undated (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides Labeled "VA", undated (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Devils T", undated (Box 41)
  - Box of Slides, unlabeled, undated (Box 41)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "Taos - Red River" 1957, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Sheredan" 1955, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled: "State Fair & Rainy Mt." 1953, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Cal", undated (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Scott Thomas Family?" 1956, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides unlabeled 1955, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides lunabeled 1954, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Yello Stone" 1956, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Garden of Gods" 1955, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Philbrook" 1958, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides unlabeled 1955, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Sheridan- Colo, Cabezon" 1954, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Candlestick and Graduation?", undated (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides unlabeled 1954, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Indians" 1955, circa 1950s (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Via Coeli", undated (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Arts and Crafts Fair", undated (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "A.M.A. Ft. Defiance, VA", undated (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Momaday 195", undated (Box 43)
  - Box of 2¾x2¾ photographic slides unlabeled, undated (Box 43)
  - Box of 2¾x2¾ photographic slides unlabeled, undated (Box 43)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides unlabeled 1955, circa 1950s (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "NY and Wash", undated (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Cal", undated (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Cal", undated (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Cal", undated (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Bishops Lodge Acoma", undated (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides unlabeled, undated (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Gallup Ceremonials" 1954, circa 1950s (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Vallecitos Country" 1953, circa 1950s (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Santa Barbara Christmas 1964", circa 1960s (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled :Acoma - Sky City" 1952, circa 1950s (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Scott in Graduation Gown", undated (Box 44)
  - Box of 2x2 photographic slides labeled "Delores", undated (Box 44)
  - Envelope of 2¾x2¾ photographic slides unlabeled, undated (Box 44)
  - Envelope of 2¾x2¾ photographic slides unlabeled, undated (Box 44)
  - Envelope of photographic negative strips, undated (Box 44)
  - Envelope of misc. small family photos, unlabeled and undated. (Box 44)
  - Framed certificate to Natachee from the U.S. Department of the Interior. Honor award for "Meritorious Service" signed by Roger C.B. Morton, Secretary on the Interior, 1972, circa 1970s (Box 47)
  - Print of the cover of Native People's Arts & Lifeways magazine with NSM on the cover, Nov/Dec/ 2003., circa 2000s (Box 47)
  - News clipping of Natachee teaching in My Weekly Reader: The Children's Newspaper Vol. XXXIV, Issue 3, Sept. 28-Oct 2, 1964, circa 1960s (Box 47)
  - Large booklet/folder "Seminar in Native American Studies, Spello Italy. Sept. 4-8, 2000." NSM taught a 5 housr course on Oral Tradition, circa 2000s (Box 47)
  - Booklet from Universite Blaise Pascal Clermont-Ferrand, La Grande Experience de l'Equilibre des Liqueurs, undated (Box 47)
  - Hardbound copy of Life magazine special edition "Out Indian Heritage" 1971 with article "A Vision Beyond Time and Place" by NSM on page 67. The cover also had Al Momaday's name inscribed, circa 1970s (Box 47)
  - The National Medal of Arts to NSM, November 2007 and The Oklahoma City National Memorial and Museum Reflections of Hope Award to NSM April 19, 2005, circa 2000s (Box 47)
  - Book: The Great Artists: A Library of their lives, times and paintings: Picasso 1978, circa 1970s (Box 47)
  - Portrait of NSM in a mat folder, by G.H. Sollier, 1956, circa 1950s (Box 48)
  - Embossed prints in mats, "The Raven and the First Men" and "The Bear Mother" both by Bill Reid, date unknown, undated (Box 48)
  - Unnamed watercolor paintings from an artist scrapbook, most likely NSM's work, but unsigned, undated (Box 48)
  - Lamenated poster for 1999 Red Earth Festival where NSM received the Red Earth Ambassador of the Year Award with NSM picture, circa 1990s (Box 48)
  - Calendar: Navajo Calendric Cycle, 1967, circa 1960s (Box 48)
  - Oklahoma governor's commendation "Spirit Award" to NSM 2003; Oklahoma governor's commendation for being one of 50 Oklahomans of the century, 2000, circa 2000s (Box 48)
  - State of Oklahoma "Citation of Artstic Excellence" to NSM, date unknown c. 2000s, circa 2000s (Box 48)
  - Poster of NSM, 1980; Poster for the New Mexico D.H. Lawrence Festival in NSM listed as presenter, undated; Poster for a reading from House Made of Dawn, undated, circa 1980s (Box 48)
  - Menu from Alois Dallmayr Restaurant in Germany, 1985, circa 1980s (Box 49)
  - Two Copies of Encantos Magazine, 1971 with NSM on page 14, circa 1970s (Box 49)
  - The New York Times Magazine: The Sophisticated Traveler, 1988 with an article by NSM "Sacred and Ancestral Ground" on page 28; The New York Times Magazine: The Sophisticated Traveler, 1986 with an article "On Bavarian Byways" on page 28, circa 1980s (Box 49)
  - The New York Times Magazine: The Sophisticated Traveler, 1992 with an article "New Mexico: Passage Into Legend" by NSM on page 22; The New York Times Magazine: The Sophisticated Traveler, 1985 with an article "Discovering the Land of Light" by NSM on page 40., circa 1980s (Box 49)
  - Courier-Journal Magazine March 26, 1978 with a story on the whole Momaday family on page 7; The New York Times Book Reviews Jan. 1967 with a review by NSM on page 20, circa 1970s (Box 49)
  - Two copies of California Living with an artile on NSM on page 6, 1969, circa 1960s (Box 49)
  - Four copies of Life "Our Indian Heritage" 1971 with article "A Vision Beyond Time and Place" by NSM on page 67, circa 1970s (Box 49)
  - Four copies of Life "Our Indian Heritage" 1971 with article "A Vision Beyond Time and Place" by NSM on page 67, circa 1970s (Box 49)
  - Three copies of Alququerque Journal Arts section with a story of NSM on the cover with his artwork, May 1989, circa 1980s (Box 50)
  - Oklahoma Gazette May 2006, with article on NSM on page 54; The Oklahoman Weekend Look section May, 2006 with an art review of NSM work on page 15D, circa 2000s (Box 50)
  - Six copies of Santa Fe Reporter January 20-26, 2010 with NSM on the cover and an article on him on page 14., circa 2010s (Box 50)
  - Five copies of Santa Fe Reporter January 20-26, 2010 with NSM on the cover and an article on him on page 14., circa 2010s (Box 50)
  - Albuquerque Journal Recreation section, March 1988., circa 1980s (Box 50)
  - Two copies of New York Newsday Ideas 1986 with article on page 7 by NSM "A Centennial Feting Our Own Imagination", circa 1980s (Box 50)
  - News clipping from the Arizona Daily Star, 1992 on "The Literary West"; New York Times book reviews, 1984; The American Poetry Review 1984 with interview of NSM by Joseph Bruchac, circa 1980s (Box 50)
  - Two Copies of New World Times Dedicated to the renaissance of the American Indian, Fall 1991. Interview with NSM page 33, circa 1990s (Box 50)
  - Large photocopies of an article: "La Derniere Des Grandes Favorites Dans' L'Essone, 1971" with a note all in archival folders, circa 1970s (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Sonia Sotomayor; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Sonia Sotomayor; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Janet Napolitano; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Janet Napolitano; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Sunita Williams; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Sunita Williams; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Albert Einstein; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Albert Einstein; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With John F. Kennedy; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With John F. Kennedy; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Yo-Yo Ma; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Yo-Yo Ma; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Cesar Chavez; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Cesar Chavez; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Natasha Kai; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Natasha Kai; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Marian Wright Edelman; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With Marian Wright Edelman; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With NSM; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
  - Poster: "Many Cultures One Nation" With NSM; 22h x 17 w, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))